Clara E. Sipprell Papers
Clara E. Sipprell Papers
- Negatives and proof prints
  - Gerdan Estate
    - Proof prints (Box 82)
  - Geribord, Mr. Donald H., 1957
    - Negatives (Box FB023)
  - Germanova, Maria N. and Alexander Kallinsky (Moscow)
    - Negatives (Box 53)
    - Negatives (Box FB023)
    - Negatives (Box FB164)
  - Getman, Mr. William T.
    - Negatives (Box FB023)
    - Proof prints (Box 77)
  - Gibbs, Mrs. Edwin
    - Negatives (Box FB107)
  - Gibson, Miss Eleanor, 1962
    - Negatives (Box 50)
    - Negatives (Box FB023)
    - Negatives (Box FB154)
  - Gibson, Miss Eleanor, 1963
    - Negatives (Box FB023)
    - Proof prints (Box 77)
  - Gibson, Mrs. James P. and daughter Mrs. Lewis Daniel and granddaughter Deborah (Lake Placid Club), 1953
    - Negatives (Box FB107)
    - Negatives (Box FB108)
    - Proof prints (Box 83)
  - Gibson, Mrs. James R., 1955
    - Negatives (Box FB108)
    - Proof prints (Box 77)
  - Giffin, ----, 1967
    - Negatives (Box FB023)
  - Gilbert, Anna, 1961
    - Negatives (Box 50)
    - Negatives (Box 64)
    - Negatives (Box FB023)
    - Negatives (Box FB154)
  - Gilbreth, Dr. Lillian, and Mrs. Wallace, 1956
    - Negatives (Box 50)
    - Negatives (Box FB024)
    - Negatives (Box FB154)
    - Proof prints (Box 77)
  - Gilihust, Mrs. Arlington
    - Negatives (Box FB024)
  - Gillet, Mrs. H.M. (2300 Centre Street, Bay City MI)
    - Proof prints (Box 77)
  - Gillman, ----, 1966
    - Negatives (Box 50)
    - Negatives (Box FB024)
    - Negatives (Box FB154)
    - Proof prints (Box 77)
  - Gilmore, Mrs. Voit, group (Southern Pines), 1953
    - Negatives (Box FB108)
  - Giunta, Carol (Fenner?) and Aldo, 1957
    - Negatives (Box FB024)
  - Gladstone, Mrs. Nathan and 2 daughters, 1957
    - Negatives (Box FB024)
  - Glenn, James, 1963
    - Negatives (Box FB024)
  - Godfrey, Doris, 1967
    - Negatives (Box FB024)
    - Proof prints (Box 77)
  - Godfrey, Lt. Gordon and Mrs.
    - Negatives (Box FB024)
  - Golokvastoff, George [Russian poet]
    - Negatives (Box 50)
    - Negatives (Box FB108)
  - Goodrich, Arthur (Norwich, VT)
    - Negatives (Box FB108)
    - Proof prints (Box 83)
  - Gordon-Smith, Beatrice (niece's wedding)
    See also Fry, Lois (niece of Beatrice Gordon-Smith) and Smith, Miss Beatrice Gordon.
    - Negatives (Box FB024)
  - Gould, Mr.
    - Negatives (Box FB024)
    - Proof prints (Box 77)
  - Grand Canyon
    - Negatives (Box FB108)
  - Grand Duchess Marie
    - Negatives (Box 50)
    - Negatives (Box FB108)
  - Grebenshikoff, Georges
    - Negatives (Box FB154)
    - Negatives (Box 50)
  - [Grebenshikoff?] Grefeushikoff, Mr.
    - Negatives (Box FB024)
    - Proof prints (Box 77)
  - [Grebenshikoff?] Greteushikoff and Roerich [Nikolai Konstantinovich Rerikh]
    - Negatives (Box FB024)
  - [Grebenshikoff?] Gretcheminoff
    - Negatives (Box FB024)
  - Green (grandchildren of Mrs. W.E. Green)
    - Negatives (Box FB108)
    - Negatives (Box FB109)
    - Proof prints (Box 83)
  - Green, Alison (daughter of Mrs. Horace Green)
    - Negatives (Box FB109)
    - Proof prints (Box 83)
  - Green, Anne Bosworth, 1939
    - Negatives (Box 50)
    - Negatives (Box FB109)
    - Negatives (Box FB154)
  - Green, Felicity, 1967
    - Negatives (Box FB024)
  - Green, Lois
    - Negatives (Box FB109)
  - Green, Nat
    - Negatives (Box FB024)
    - Proof prints (Box 77)
  - Gregorian, Boris
    - Proof prints (Box 77)
  - Griffith, Dr. Helen (Mt. Holyoke)
    - Negatives (Box FB024)
    - Proof prints (Box 77)
  - Griffith, Dr. Wayne, 1959
    - Negatives (Box FB024)
    - Proof prints (Box 77)
  - Griffith, Judge (Manchester)
    - Negatives (Box FB024)
    - Proof prints (Box 77)
  - Gruver, Mrs. Earl S.
    - Negatives (Box FB109)
  - Guen, Louise
    - Negatives (Box FB024)
  - Guilder, Mrs. Rodwan
    - Negatives (Box FB109)
  - Gulick, Leeds and family
    - Negatives (Box FB109)
  - Gulick, Mrs. Leeds and father
    - Negatives (Box FB024)
  - Gulick, Leeds family
    - Negatives (Box FB109)
  - Gund, Henry
    - Negatives (Box FB109)
    - Proof prints (Box 83)
  - Gund, Henry Jr.
    - Negatives (Box 50)
    - Negatives (Box FB109)
    - Negatives (Box FB154)
  - Gunternan, Miss Bertha
    - Negatives (Box FB110)
  - Gurney, Mrs.
    - Negatives (Box FB110)
  - Gustav V, King of Sweden, 1938
    - Negatives (Box FB025)
  - Gustav VI, King of Sweden, and Crown Princess Louise, 1938
    - Negatives (Box FB025)
  - Haag, 1957
    - Negatives (Box FB025)
  - Hadorn, Rosa
    - Negatives (Box FB025)
  - Hadrian's villa (Rome)
    - Negatives (Box 50)
    - Negatives (Box FB199)
  - Hafford, Mrs. Paul and family
    - Negatives (Box FB025)
  - Hagadorn, Beulah
    - Negatives (Box 50)
    - Negatives (Box FB025)
    - Negatives (Box FB154)
  - Hagadorn, Rev. (father of Beulah), 1963
    - Negatives (Box FB025)
  - Hagelin, ----
    - Negatives (Box FB025)
    - Proof prints (Box 77)
  - Hagelin, Boris, 1942
    - Negatives (Box FB025)
    - Proof prints (Box 77)
  - Hagelin, Mrs. Boris
    - Negatives (Box FB025)
  - Hagelin, Margarita
    - Negatives (Box FB025)
  - Haggerty, Mrs. M.L., 1956
    - Negatives (Box FB025)
    - Proof prints (Box 77)
  - Hale, Earl (Eau Clair, MN)
    - Negatives (Box FB110)
    - Proof prints (Box 83)
  - Hale, Mrs. E.W. (dog, Old Bennington, VT)
    - Negatives (Box FB025)
  - Hales, Mrs. Edwin (house, Old Bennington, VT
    - Negatives (Box 50)
    - Negatives (Box FB110)
    - Negatives (Box FB154)
  - Hall, Dick (house, Hanover)
    - Negatives (Box 50)
    - Negatives (Box FB026)
    - Negatives (Box FB154)
    - Proof prints (Box 78)
  - Hall, Mrs. Frank G., 1958
    - Negatives (Box FB026)
    - Proof prints (Box 78)
  - Hall, Mrs. Henry B.
    - Negatives (Box FB110)
  - Halsey, Catherine
    - Negatives (Box FB026)
  - Halsey, Eleanor
    - Negatives (Box FB026)
    - Proof prints (Box 78)
  - Halsey, Mr. and Mrs. Charles, 1956
    - Negatives (Box 50)
    - Negatives (Box FB026)
    - Negatives (Box FB155)
  - Halt, Mrs. Beryl M.
    - Negatives (Box FB026)
  - Hamilton, ----
    - Negatives (Box FB026)
  - Hamilton, Corent Hugo
    - Negatives (Box FB026)
  - Hamilton, Florence
    - Negatives (Box 50)
    - Negatives (Box FB155)
    - Proof prints (Box 78)
  - Hamilton, Hugo
    - Negatives (Box 50)
    - Negatives (Box FB026)
    - Negatives (Box FB110)
    - Negatives (Box FB155)
  - Hammarskjold, Hjalmar, of Sweden, 1938
    - Negatives (Box FB026)
  - Hammond, John Henry, Jr.
    - Negatives (Box FB027)
    - Proof prints (Box 78)
  - Hammond, Mr. John H. and Estele (daughter of Mrs. John Henry Hammond), bridal
    - Negatives (Box FB027)
    - Proof prints (Box 78)
  - Hammond, Mrs. John Henry, 1948
    - Negatives (Box FB110)
  - Hampton Institute (Virginia), 1941
    - Negatives (Box 50)
    - Negatives (Box 64)
    - Negatives (Box FB155)
  - Hampton, LT. LP., Bly
    - Negatives (Box FB027)
  - Hamrah, Miss Claire
    - Negatives (Box FB027)
  - Hanaver (children)
    - Negatives (Box FB110)
    - Proof prints (Box 83)
  - Hancock, Natalie (daughter)
    - Negatives (Box FB110)
  - Hand, Mr. and Mrs. Walter Jr., and 1 of Walter as a soldier
    - Negatives (Box FB027)
  - Hanover
    - Negatives (Box 50)
    - Negatives (Box 64)
    - Negatives (Box FB111)
    - Negatives (Box FB155)
  - Hanover, NH (covered bridge)
    - Negatives (Box 50)
    - Negatives (Box 64)
  - Hansl, Mrs. Eva
    - Negatives (Box 50)
    - Negatives (Box FB155)
  - Hapkins, Pauline
    - Negatives (Box FB111)
  - Harbison, Georgiana Brown
    - Negatives (Box FB111)
    - Proof prints (Box 78)
  - Hard, Margaret
    - Negatives (Box 50)
    - Negatives (Box FB155)
    - Negatives, 1968 (Box FB027)
  - Hard, Walter
    - Negatives (Box FB111)
  - Hard, Walter and Margaret, 1956
    - Negatives (Box FB027)
    - Proof prints (Box 78)
  - Hard, Walter Rian Hard
    - Negatives (Box FB027)
    - Proof prints (Box 78)
  - Hard, Walter Rice, 1944
    - Negatives (Box FB027)
  - Hardy, Mr. and Mrs. Anton
    - Negatives (Box FB027)
    - Proof prints (Box 78)
  - Hardy, John A., 1940
    - Negatives (Box FB027)
    - Proof prints (Box 78)
  - Hardy, Mrs. John A. Jr.
    - Negatives (Box FB027)
    - Proof prints (Box 78)
  - Hardy, Mrs. John A. Jr. and children
    - Negatives (Box FB027)
    - Proof prints (Box 78)
  - Harkness, Mr. James
    - Negatives (Box FB188)
  - Harkness, Ruth
    - Negatives (Box 50)
    - Negatives (Box FB027)
    - Negatives (Box FB111)
    - Negatives (Box FB155)
  - D'Aposteno, Mr. and Mrs. Harmon
    - Negatives (Box FB094)
    - Negatives (Box FB111)
  - Harney, Christine, 1937
    - Negatives (Box FB111)
  - Harris, Miss Elizabeth (Hampton)
    - Negatives (Box 50)
    - Negatives (Box FB027)
    - Negatives (Box FB155)
  - Harris, Mrs. Elizabeth Page, 1962
    - Negatives (Box FB027)
  - Harris, Rev. Carter H. and Mrs.
    - Negatives (Box FB027)
  - Harris, Reverend Gertrude, 1964
    - Negatives (Box 50)
    - Negatives (Box FB027)
    - Negatives (Box FB155)
    - Proof prints (Box 78)
  - Harris, Roy, 1940
    - Negatives (Box 50)
    - Negatives (Box FB028)
    - Negatives (Box FB155)
  - Harris, Theodore and Bob
    - Negatives (Box FB028)
  - Harrison, Mrs. Carter H.
    - Negatives (Box FB112)
  - Harrison, Mrs. St. B. (Canadian, 123 Westward Rd, Lakeview Park, Ashville 54575)
    - Negatives (Box FB028)
  - Hartneet
    - Negatives (Box FB028)
  - Harvey, Mrs. A.S. (Sajman), 1939
    - Negatives (Box FB112)
    - Proof prints (Box 83)
  - Hassel (group of 2)
    - Negatives (Box FB028)
  - Hastings, Daniel O., Senator and Mrs., 1955
    - Negatives (Box FB112)
    - Proof prints (Box 78)
  - Hastings, Sybil
    - Proof prints (Box 78)
  - Hatch, Mrs. Harold (home in Sharon, Conn.)
    - Negatives (Box 50)
    - Negatives (Box FB156)
  - Hunt, Naomi
    - Negatives (Box FB030)
  - Havens, Mrs. S.M., 1957
    - Negatives (Box FB028)
    - Proof prints (Box 78)
  - Hawk, Mrs.
    - Negatives (Box FB028)
  - Hawkes, Martin, 1967
    - Negatives (Box 50)
    - Negatives (Box FB028)
    - Negatives (Box FB156)
    - Proof prints (Box 78)
  - Hawkridge, Mrs. Leslie (Newton Center, Mass)
    - Negatives (Box FB189)
  - Hawley, ---- (baby of Mr. and Mrs. Burnham Hawley)
    - Negatives (Box FB028)
  - Hawley, Mrs. Burnham
    - Negatives (Box FB112)
    - Proof prints (Box 83)
  - Hayashi, Keiko, I Nouve
    - Negatives (Box FB112)
  - Hayden, Mrs. Warren, 1957
    - Negatives (Box FB028)
    - Proof prints (Box 78)
  - Hayes, Roland, 1964
    - Negatives (Box 50)
    - Negatives (Box FB028)
    - Negatives (Box FB156)
  - Hazard, Liverpool and others; Georgia and others; St. Simon's
    - Negatives (Box 50)
  - Hazen, ----
    - Negatives (Box 50)
    - Negatives (Box FB189)
    - Negatives (Box FB199)
  - Head [Heard?], Mrs. F.
    - Negatives (Box FB156)
    - Negatives (Box 51)
  - Heath, Mrs. Benjamin and family (daughter of Mrs. Buckley)
    - Negatives (Box FB029)
  - Hehmeyer, ----
    - Negatives (Box FB112)
  - Helms and Nina [Cekich], 1959
    - Negatives (Box FB074)
  - Helms, Dr. and Mrs. William K. and Nina (Steubenville, Ohio), 1956
    - Negatives (Box FB074)
  - Helms, Mr. and Mrs. William K. Jr., Nina and Peter Nicolas [Nina's son]
    - Proof prints (Box 80)
  - Helms, Nina and Kathy, 1963
    - Negatives (Box FB074)
  - Helms, Peter [Nina's son], 1956
    - Negatives (Box 51)
    - Negatives (Box 64)
    - Negatives (Box FB074)
    - Negatives (Box FB156)
  - Helms, Peter [Nina's son], 1963
    - Negatives (Box FB074)
  - Heminway, Father (Sherbonn)
    - Negatives (Box 51)
    - Negatives (Box FB029)
    - Negatives (Box FB156)
    - Proof prints (Box 78)
  - Henagin, Peter
    - Negatives (Box FB112)
    - Proof prints (Box 83)
  - Henick, Prudence
    - Negatives (Box FB112)
  - Henry, Jean and dog
    - Negatives (Box 51)
    - Negatives (Box FB112)
    - Negatives (Box FB156)
    - Proof prints (Box 78)
  - Herbert, Mrs. John A. (Dorset)
    - Negatives (Box FB029)
  - Herrick, Mrs. W.C.
    - Negatives (Box FB029)
  - Herring, Elizabeth
    - Negatives (Box FB112)
  - Heufsch, Mrs. B.W.
    - Negatives (Box FB029)
  - Hewitt, Mrs. Clifford (family)
    - Negatives (Box 51)
    - Negatives (Box FB112)
    - Negatives (Box FB156)
    - Proof prints (Box 83)
  - Hicks, Granville
    - Negatives (Box 51)
    - Negatives (Box FB029)
  - Hiel, Patty
    - Glass plate negative (Box 69-01)
  - Higgins, Mrs. Aldus
    - Negatives (Box FB029)
    - Proof prints (Box 78)
  - Hilbert, Mrs. Christine
    - Negatives (Box FB112)
    - Negatives (Box FB113)
    - Negatives (Box FB196)
    - Proof prints (Box 83)
  - Hill (house)
    - Negatives (Box 51)
    - Negatives (Box FB199)
  - Hill, Mr. and Mrs. Jay Stuart (Trenton, NJ), 1953
    - Negatives (Box FB113)
  - Hill, Mrs.
    - Negatives (Box FB189)
  - Hill, Mrs. John and daughter Alex
    - Proof prints (Box 78)
  - Hill, Mrs. Eleva
    - Negatives (Box FB029)
  - Hillwan, Mr. H.M. (Lake Placid Club), 1953
    - Proof prints (Box 78)
  - Hink, Mrs. C.C.
    - Negatives (Box FB113)
  - Hinkley, Mrs. J.W. Sr.
    - Negatives (Box 51)
    - Negatives (Box FB113)
    - Negatives (Box FB114)
    - Negatives (Box FB156)
    - Proof prints (Box 83)
  - Ho, Mrs.
    - Negatives (Box FB114)
  - Hoag, Charles Makin
    - Negatives (Box FB029)
  - Hochstaller, ----
    - Negatives (Box FB029)
  - Hodges, ----
    - Negatives (Box 51)
    - Negatives (Box FB029)
    - Negatives (Box FB156)
    - Proof prints (Box 78)
  - Hodgman, Mrs. Jean, 1951
    - Negatives (Box FB114)
  - Hoeing, Mr. Frederick W. (25 Tudor City Place, N.Y. 17 N.Y.)
    - Negatives (Box 51)
    - Negatives (Box FB029)
    - Negatives (Box FB156)
  - Hoeing, Mrs. Charles, 1955
    - Proof prints (Box 78)
  - Hoffman, Josefa
    - Negatives (Box FB029)
  - Hoffman, Malvina
    - Negatives (Box 51)
    - Negatives (Box FB029)
    - Negatives (Box FB156)
  - Hoffman, Miss Hester R. (North Hampton, MA)
    - Negatives (Box FB189)
  - Hofmann, Josefa
    - Negatives (Box 51)
  - Holbrook, Miss Etta
    - Negatives (Box FB114)
  - Hollyhock
    - Negatives (Box FB114)
  - Holmes, Oliver Wendell
    - Negatives (Box FB029)
  - Homer, Helen, 1960
    - Negatives (Box FB029)
  - Honskeeper, Mr.
    - Negatives (Box FB029)
    - Negatives (Box FB156)
    - Proof prints (Box 78)
  - Hopkins, Mrs. L.A. (daughter of Mrs. Edwin Mill), 1955
    - Negatives (Box FB114)
  - Horring, ---- (daughter of Mr. Walter Horring)
    - Negatives (Box FB114)
  - Horshorn, Mrs. Harvey
    - Negatives (Box FB114)
  - Hosborn, Mrs. Harvey and children
    - Negatives (Box FB114)
  - Houghton, Mrs. Agnes, 1958
    - Negatives (Box 51)
    - Negatives (Box FB029)
    - Negatives (Box FB156)
  - House in winter
    - Negatives (Box FB189)
  - Houses and interiors
    - Negatives (Box 51)
    - Negatives (Box FB030)
    - Negatives (Box FB156)
  - Howard, Mrs. Velma
    - Negatives (Box FB115)
  - Howe, Carlton
    - Negatives (Box FB030)
  - Hoyle, Dr. and Mrs. E. Petrie (Spruce Creek Bend, Kittery, Maine)
    - Negatives (Box FB115)
  - Hoyt, ---- (2 sons), 1955
    - Proof prints (Box 78)
  - Hoyt, Anne (home of, Sharon)
    - Negatives (Box 51)
    - Negatives (Box FB030)
    - Negatives (Box FB156)
    - Proof prints (Box 78)
  - Hoyt, Anne Sherwan
    - Negatives (Box FB030)
  - Hubbard, Mrs. William H.
    - Negatives (Box FB115)
    - Proof prints (Box 83)
  - Hufford, Mrs. Paul and Phillip
    - Negatives (Box FB115)
    - Proof prints (Box 83)
  - Hufford, Priscilla (daughter of Mr. and Mrs. Paul Hufford)
    - Negatives (Box FB115)
  - Hughes, ---- (Miss Jeannie E. Hughes' mother)
    - Negatives (Box FB115)
  - Hughes, Langston
    - Negatives (Box 51)
    - Negatives (Box FB115)
    - Negatives (Box FB156)
    - Proof prints (Box 78)
  - Hulst, Margaret, 1940
    - Negatives (Box FB115)
  - Humphrey, Walt S., 1939
    - Negatives (Box FB030)
  - Humphrey, Zephine
    - Negatives (Box 51)
  - Hunter, Mrs. Frederick
    - Negatives (Box 51)
    - Negatives (Box FB030)
    - Negatives (Box FB156)
    - Proof prints (Box 78)
  - Huntington, Mr. and Mrs. George, 1936
    - Negatives (Box FB116)
  - Huntington, Mary
    - Negatives (Box FB116)
    - Proof prints (Box 83)
  - Iveson, Phoebe
    - Negatives (Box FB030)
  - Inukai
    - Negatives (Box 51)
    - Negatives (Box FB116)
    - Negatives (Box FB156)
  - Isenberg, Mr. Abraham, 1958
    - Negatives (Box FB030)
    - Proof prints (Box 78)
  - Isenberg, Mrs. Abraham, 1958
    - Negatives (Box 51)
    - Negatives (Box FB030)
    - Negatives (Box FB157)
    - Proof prints (Box 78)
  - Ivanoff, Vladimir
    - Negatives (Box FB030)
    - Negatives (Box FB189)
  - Iveson, ----
    - Negatives (Box FB116)
  - Jareska, Mrs. Louise Llewellyn (897 2nd Ave, NY, 17, PL 3-2694
    - Negatives (Box FB116)
  - Jareski, Todeus
    - Negatives (Box FB116)
  - Jeffers, Mrs. G.A.
    - Negatives (Box FB116)
  - Jeffers, Robinson, 1941
    - Negatives (Box 51)
    - Negatives (Box FB030)
    - Negatives (Box FB157)
    - Proof prints (Box 78)
  - Jeffries, Mr. Bruce (904 Court St., Jamesville, WI)
    - Negatives (Box FB117)
    - Proof prints (Box 83)
  - Jeffries, Miss. Ruth B. (602 South 3rd, Jamesville, WI)
    - Negatives (Box FB116)
    - Negatives (Box FB117)
    - Proof prints (Box 83)
  - Jewett, Mrs. Harry M., 1926
    - Negatives (Box FB117)
  - Johnson, ---- (daughter of Mrs. Oscar Johnson)
    - Negatives (Box FB030)
  - Johnson, Mrs. Clark
    - Negatives (Box FB117)
  - Johnson, Oscar (family)
    - Negatives (Box FB117)
    - Negatives (Box FB118)
  - Johnson, Mrs. Robert and baby
    - Negatives (Box FB117)
  - Johnsons, ---- (bride, daughter of Mr. and Mrs. Edward Johnsons)
    - Negatives (Box FB118)
    - Proof prints (Box 83)
  - Johnstone, Mrs. J.B.
    - Negatives (Box FB118)
  - Jolley, Mrs.
    - Negatives (Box FB118)
  - Jones, Mrs. Adam Leroy
    - Negatives (Box FB031)
    - Proof prints (Box 78)
  - Jones, Caroline
    - Negatives (Box FB030)
  - Jones, Mrs. J.F., 1957
    - Negatives (Box FB031)
    - Proof prints (Box 78)
  - Jones, Mary Hoxie, 1960
    - Negatives (Box 51)
    - Negatives (Box FB031)
    - Negatives (Box FB157)
  - Jones, Rufus (South China, Pendle Hill), 1958
    - Negatives (Box 51)
    - Negatives (Box FB031)
    - Negatives (Box FB157)
    - Proof prints (Box 78)
  - Jones, Mrs. Ruth Addison
    - Negatives (Box FB118)
    - Proof prints (Box 83)
  - Jourard, Paul, 1963
    - Negatives (Box 51)
    - Negatives (Box FB031)
    - Negatives (Box FB157)
    - Proof prints (Box 78)
  - Joy, Mr. and Mrs. Shelley
    - Negatives (Box FB031)
    - Proof prints (Box 78)
  - Kahn, Albert (more in NY)
    - Negatives (Box FB031)
  - Kahn, Mr. Albert (208 Mack Street, Detroit, MI)
    - Negatives (Box FB118)
  - Kahn, Mrs., 1967
    - Negatives (Box FB031)
    - Proof prints (Box 78)
  - Kane, Mr. and Mrs. Thomas (daughter and baby, granddaughter, Goodwyne, PA), 1956
    - Negatives (Box FB031)
    - Proof prints (Box 78)
  - Kane, Mrs. Thomas (granddaughter)
    - Negatives (Box FB031)
  - Kane, Mrs. Thomas L.
    - Negatives (Box 51)
    - Negatives (Box FB157)
  - Karasz, Honka
    - Negatives (Box FB118)
  - Karasz, [Honka?]
    - Negatives (Box 51)
    - Negatives (Box FB118)
  - Karasz, [Honka?] and Peterson
    - Negatives (Box FB118)
  - Kaufman, Mrs. Max, 1926
    - Negatives (Box FB031)
  - Kaufman, Mrs. Max and Peter
    - Negatives (Box FB118)
  - Kaufman, Mrs. Max at L.P., 1929
    - Negatives (Box FB031)
  - Kaufman, Mrs. Max (Rockridge), 1927
    - Negatives (Box 51)
    - Negatives (Box 64)
    - Negatives (Box FB031)
    - Negatives (Box FB032)
  - Kaufman, Max (son Peter)
    - Negatives (Box FB032)
    - Negatives (Box FB118)
    - Negatives (Box FB119)
    - Negatives (Box FB189)
    - Proof prints (Box 78)
  - Kaufman, Peter, 1932
    - Negatives (Box 51)
    - Negatives (Box FB032)
    - Negatives (Box FB119)
    - Negatives (Box FB157)
    - Proof prints (Box 78)
    - Proof prints (Box 83)
  - Kaufman, Peter (child of, as infant)
    - Negatives (Box FB119)
  - Kelley, Dr. (Mrs. Lytle Hunter)
    - Negatives (Box FB119)
  - Kelley, Father
    - Negatives (Box 51)
  - Kelley, Mrs. Linwood
    - Negatives (Box FB032)
  - Kellogg, ----
    - Negatives (Box FB032)
  - Kellogg, Mrs. L.W., 1935
    - Negatives (Box FB120)
  - Kellogg, Mrs. Lida
    See also Maury, Lois K. (Keels Wedding and Lida Kellogg).
    - Negatives (Box 51)
    - Negatives (Box FB032)
    - Negatives (Box FB157)
    - Proof prints (Box 78)
  - Kellogg, Lida (Manchester), 1944
    - Negatives (Box FB032)
  - Kellogg, Lida (Silvermine house and grounds), 1940
    - Negatives (Box FB119)
    - Proof prints (Box 78)
  - [Kellogg], Lida and Lois [Maury] in the garden, 1950
    - Negatives (Box FB123)
  - Kellogg, Spencer Jr.
    - Negatives (Box FB032)
  - Kelly, Mr. and Mrs. W.A. and son Fred
    - Negatives (Box FB120)
    - Proof prints (Box 78)
  - Kennedy, Charles Rann
    - Negatives (Box 51)
  - Kenworthy, Mrs. A.V., 1970
    - Negatives (Box 51)
    - Negatives (Box FB032)
    - Negatives (Box FB157)
  - Ketchum, Mr.and Mrs. E.C.
    - Negatives (Box FB032)
  - Keyes, Dr. Harold, 1960
    - Negatives (Box 51)
    - Negatives (Box FB032)
    - Negatives (Box FB157)
    - Proof prints (Box 78)
  - Khrabroff, ---- (kitchen group, with Aunt Bina etc.), 1934
    - Negatives (Box FB120)
  - Khrabroff, Babat and Deda
    - Negatives (Box FB120)
  - Khrabroff, Gen. Nicolas and Nina at 12
    - Negatives (Box 51)
    - Negatives (Box 64)
    - Negatives (Box FB120)
    - Negatives (Box FB157)
  - Khrabroff, General and Mme. on winter road
    - Negatives (Box FB196)
  - Khrabroff, Irina
    - Negatives (Box FB120)
  - Khrabroff, family group (Thetford)
    - Negatives (Box FB189)
  - Kidder, Mrs. E.H.
    - Negatives (Box FB032)
  - Kidder, Mrs. F.T.
    - Negatives (Box FB032)
    - Negatives (Box FB120)
  - Kiernan, ----
    - Negatives (Box FB033)
    - Proof prints (Box 78)
  - Kiggins, Mr. Gilbert and fiancee, 1956
    - Negatives (Box 51)
    - Negatives (Box FB033)
    - Negatives (Box FB157)
    - Proof prints (Box 78)
  - Kiggins, Mrs. Gilbert, as bride, 1956
    - Negatives (Box 51)
    - Negatives (Box FB033)
    - Negatives (Box FB157)
    - Proof prints (Box 78)
  - Kiggins, Mrs. Gilbert (baby of), 1960
    - Negatives (Box 51)
    - Negatives (Box FB033)
    - Negatives (Box FB157)
  - King, Billy (son of Mrs. Donald King)
    - Negatives (Box 51)
  - King, Faith and Bill, and families, 1966
    - Negatives (Box FB033)
    - Proof prints (Box 78)
  - King, Mrs. Donald, 1962
    - Negatives (Box FB033)
    - Proof prints (Box 78)
  - Kingsley, Mrs. Darwin
    - Proof prints (Box 79)
  - Kinney, Mrs. Mary and children, 1953
    - Proof prints (Box 79)
  - Kirkbane, Dr. Virgil R.D. (children)
    - Negatives (Box FB033)
    - Negatives (Box FB120)
  - Kirkland, Dr. E.
    - Negatives (Box FB033)
    - Proof prints (Box 79)
  - Kister, Hanna
    - Negatives (Box FB120)
  - Kitaldrich, Basil
    - Negatives (Box FB033)
  - Kitrell, Mrs. F.R.
    - Negatives (Box FB033)
    - Proof prints (Box 79)
  - Knapp, Betsy, 1960
    - Negatives (Box 51)
    - Negatives (Box FB157)
  - Knipper-Chekhova, Olga [wife of Anton Chekov]
    - Negatives (Box FB189)
  - Knothe, Mrs. Alex, 1961
    - Negatives (Box FB033)
    - Proof prints (Box 79)
  - Konenkov, Sergei
    See also Einstein, Albert with Konenkov.
    - Negatives (Box 52)
    - Negatives (Box 64)
    - Negatives (Box FB034)
    - Negatives (Box FB158)
    - Negatives (Box FB199)
    - Negatives, 1928 (Box FB034)
    - Negatives, 1935 (Box FB120)
    - Negatives, 1936 (Box FB120)
    - Negatives, 1937 (Box FB120)
    - Negatives, 1938 (Box FB120)
  - Konenkov, Sergei, with god-daughter Nina
    See also [Cekich], Nina with god father Segei Konenkov
    - Negatives (Box 52)
    - Negatives (Box 64)